





in linkedin.com/in/thom-prayon



https://github.com/tompra



https://tomprayondev.netlify.app/

### **SKILLS & TOOLS**

# **Frontend Development**

HTML CSS Javascript **TypeScript** 

jQuery

**Boostrap** 

Material UI

React

Angular

React Native

Expo

Progressive Web Apps

## **Backend Development**

Node.js

APIs (JSON, RESTful)

Hosting & Web Services (AWS,

Google Firestore, OnRender,

Netlify)

**PostgreSQL** 

MongoDB

### **Others**

Git & Github

Test Driven Development

Postman

Trello (Kanban)

**Figma** 

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

## **EDUCATION**

Career Foundry,

Fullstack Web Development,

Sept. 2023 - Febr. 2024

Volkshochschule.

Deutschkurs B1 + B2,

Mar. 2019 - Dec. 2020

Coderhouse.

Web Development,

Jun. 2021 - Dec. 2022

Escuela Da Vinci,

Multimedia Design,

Mar. 2015 - July.2017

Universidad de Buenos Aires,

Economic Science, Mar. 2012 - Nov.2014

# THOMAS PRAYON

# Web Developer

### **ABOUT ME**

Web developer with a meticulous eye and passion for problem solving, whether in the digital realm or in real-life bouldering or rock-climbing. Creative with a diverse bunch of experiences from marketing and design to operations, and even tattooing. Bringing organisational and problem solving skills + a bunch of enthusiasm for learning (and developing) new technologies.

### WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

#### **Cinematix**

Personal project, Career Foundry, September - October 2023

- Created a single-page, responsive front-end application using React following the MVC design pattern.
- Built a REST API woth Node.js with Express
- Created a non-relational database using MongoDB using Moongose.
- Tested API endpoints with Postman.
- Created a well written documentation and deployed the API.
- Users can learn more about the movies they like, creating an account and save/remove their favorite movies.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Rider / RiderOps / Ops Associate Mar. 2022 - Aug. 2023 | - Berlin, DE

- [Rider Ops] Involve organizing load work for riders, making bike reports and repairs in a high-paced atmosphere.
- [Ops Associate] I consistently stock shelves with precision, optimize shelf organization to enhace overall productivity.

Tattoo Home Studio - Handpoke Dec. 2016 - Present | Buenos Aires, ARG

• Drawing and designing from paper to screen and from screen to skin.

Waiter / Cook / Organizer - Avocado Catering Mar. 2016 - Nov.2018 | Buenos Aires. ARG

- [Cook] Learning different cooking techniques, following precise instructions, and finally preparing meals at events.
- [Organizer] Coordinate all staff, creating shift plans, ensuring seamless organization and timeliness in planning. Making sure no details slips.

Junior Administrative - Promostar S.A Feb.2011 - Aug.2016 | Buenos Aires, ARG

- Managing payments, maintaining accurate bookkeeping and accounting, and implementing cost management strategies. Promostar is a marketing company with 200+ employees.
- In charge of overseeing the maintenance of all financial data and documentation.